Seino! Galgal Channel GOGO!
Today we will watch music videos!
Last time we watched The Finest, and this time we will watch IWANA Manifesto!
First time watching! First time watching! I'm looking forward to it!
Let's watch it now! Movie start!
So, everyone want to see it?
It's pretty cute right from the start.
Should I stop?
Let's just play it once.
Here we go!
Fave T-shirt.
It's like a T-shirt.
It's so cute!
You did it!
So cute!
The colors are amazing.
It looks really good.
Oh, my God.
What's that?
This?
I'm having a hard time deciding.
This one's cute.
Sing this.
Sing it.
This one's pretty good.
I like it.
Fave.
Cute.
This one.
Oh, it's calling to you.
What's that?
I like the way you know.
I like the way you dance.
What's that?
Fame!
I need a hand!
It's pulling, it's pulling.
That's fun.
Oh, my God.
I can't believe I'm watching this.
He's got you.
Oh, my God.
Do you have a Creta T-shirt?
I see.
Oh, wow.
That's nice.
That's great.
It's self-changing.
It's like a tuba pare.
That's embarrassing.
I'm getting beat up.
I'm always getting hit in the pare.
Can I have an ice cream?
You're already dressed.
I can wear it.
Can I have an ice cream?
Thank you for your time.
Oh!
Kira!
Cute.
It's just the right size.
Oh!
It's in, it's in, it's in.
It's all the way in.
This is gonna be fun.
Oh!
Are they showing each other?
Hey, I want some.
Oh, my God!
He's writing, he's writing.
They're tweeting.
Are you doing X?
I'm doing X.
X.
What's X?
He's cute.
That's a good one.
It's cute.
Thank you for your hard work.
That's good.
That el.
I got up
Haaaaah!
class
The concept of the music video is "Shikkatsu", right?
The music video is about us promoting a fictional group called Tayibu.
We've been doing a lot of different things, so I'm sure you didn't have all the information you were looking for.
It's been a long time coming.
Here's what's going on.
Did something happen? I'm curious.
Do you want me to turn my head?
Let's stop and start again, as usual.
This is really my favorite product.
It calmed me down a lot.
I like it.
The colors worked really well.
I'm really impressed.
You didn't ask, did you?
I didn't hear it.
What a surprise.
Is your keyboard okay?
This is the very last one. It's the very last one.
Yes, it is.
What's up with that?
It's cute.
What is it?
It's unusual.
It's not unusual.
It's a face.
Cut it.
They're your favorites.
It's nice.
Everyone will look at it.
It's so cute.
The colors.
I couldn't resist the T-shirts, either.
But the T-shirts were about Osaka and Osaka.
This is the kind of T-shirt, right?
You can't see it.
It wasn't used.
But it's interesting.
I took 5 shots.
He was looking back so much.
I saw that with my brother.
He told me about it.
He wants to see Claire's face.
Oh, no.
What?
Up here?
Oh, her ass?
What's it feel like?
I can't move my face.
It's been like this the whole time.
It's so cute.
Momoka's face when she's being fucked.
She's got you good, doesn't she?
What's with the nice hands?
Is it on the inside?
Inside.
Hutch Celent.
Some types don't show it.
I like it here.
Oh, it's tight.
He's cute.
I'm working on it.
I'm in a band now.
It's cool.
Here.
Yuzu, you're the focus of the drama.
Hey, you're doing great.
I heard a lot of dissonance in the studio.
Ding!
Ding.
It's hard to tell
The head tinkle is really dramatic, too.
I feel like I'm going to take this as an opportunity to do it.
I've never done it before.
People who would do it.
Yeah.
Did I do a good job with the facial expressions?
Yeah, I think so.
They're all nice people.
I don't know, the staff, they're all kind of blurry in the background.
Oh, yeah.
Fave.
With the fave stuff.
Oh, yeah.
He's behind the camera the whole time.
Like this.
Drawing...
Drawing, drawing, drawing.
I'm drawing.
I'm drawing
I clocked this so hard.
No, no, no, I have to use it, it's not good
Swell, swell
I'm using a tiny guitar
This is mishaki
It's the way he swings his hips.
Mishaki.
My hips are getting so tiny.
But I played the whole thing.
SR.
It was super fun.
It was so much fun.
It was a lot of fun.
Yes, yes, yes.
What is it?
Everyone is lined up in a row.
They're all lined up in a row, doing their thing.
That's a good idea.
They're pretending to look at their phones.
It's just pretending, but it's like they're looking at each other.
They were looking at each other.
It was crazy.
From afar, my self...
Taking pictures of everyone.
I kept showing everyone.
I was thinking about them so much.
Oh, my God.
Right here, right here.
I'm looking right here.
I can see your face right now.
He's so cute.
Good night.
I'm pretty sure I don't know what these sparkly spinning scenes are, but they're not getting any better.
Like hair.
When they get together like this...
Yus and Kira are looking at each other.
And Kira's face is really cute.
She smiles so much.
That's why it's so cute.
She told me that Kira laughs like this.
She laughs a lot, though.
She's so cute!
She said we should be together, right?
From here on, only one person from Kitano is enduring.
The scene in question.
I wonder if this was the director's order or your own decision.
Your own judgment.
That's wonderful.
There's a scene where everyone is saying, "You know, fall down," so it's probably your own decision.
But I wanted to see it like that.
I wonder how many times I've seen this, maybe the first time.
I think it's the first time. There are two standing versions, and one scene where she falls down in the three shots.
So I guess the director thought it was okay.
If so, I'm glad.
And everyone was laughing so much.
They finally laughed.
I keep dodging.
They look a little determined.
It's kind of nice that they're slowing down.
I like it.
No, I'd like to show a lot of footage.
You could try to put it in a diary or behind the scenes.
I'd like that.
A music video with just the fisheye scene.
I understand.
It's totally doable.
I thought I was using more.
We'll edit it ourselves, so please give us the video.
Sure.
I want this so bad.
Let's change the items one more time.
I can understand what's going on.
I brought the doll of the uncle in the back.
I wonder if he brought the doll.
After all, only Misaki was used.
Even Misaki did that move all the time.
The glasses.
Wearing glasses like this.
What was the concept behind that?
Concept?
Yes, that's right.
Oh, there it is. I'm sorry.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's happening.
It's Kira's timing.
She doesn't even like herself. Something's missing, isn't it?
It's me.
Oh, there it is.
She went to get it.
He's going for it. He's going for it a lot. The little thing.
He did a lot.
And a lot more.
Everyone is in the middle.
I'm going away by myself.
Freedom.
I'll multiply 75 times for Len.
That's right.
The yuzu is coming in like crazy.
Isn't it bad? No, no, no. Minami is good, too.
She has a nice face.
Isn't she cute?
This is the most fragile one.
She goes off on her own.
It's funny.
So, that was my appreciation of the music video.
Thank you very much.
I know how to dance,
I might want you to dance.
Sure. It might be easy to dance.
I'd like you to call out.
I want you to run and shout.
I'm hiccuping already.
Time to end.
That's all I'm going to say.
All the time.
So, that's it,
How was everyone?
I'm looking forward to it.
It was a great work,
I WANNA Declaration music video,
Dance Practice Video
will be uploaded from now on,
Please take a look.
So, please subscribe to our channel, click the "Good" button, and leave your comments.
Thank you very much.
This time I am wearing a costume by D-Holic.